Are you awake, Akagami?
赤神 你起来啦
I feel as if I've died and reborn.
我有种死了一次后重生于世的感觉
Reborn?
你转世了吗
I'm feeling fresh
我感觉自己很神清气爽
and fearless now.
无论遇到什么事 我现在都不会害怕了
Don't push yourself too hard.
你不要勉强自己哦
Kiki and I are going out for a bit,
我要和嬉嬉姐稍微出趟门
Mia and Kagura are already up.
米亚和神乐都已经起来了
Aren't you scared?
你这不是很害怕吗
Good morning, Akagami.
早安 赤神
Good morning, Miss Mia.
早安 米亚小姐
Where are the others?
其他人呢
Tsukuyo and Kurage are still sleeping,
月夜和海月好像还在睡
Kagura is working on her computer in her room.
神乐则是在房间里处理计算机上的工作
Kagura.
神乐
Akagami Kagura Harmony Project.
赤神神乐和和睦睦大作战
What do you want from me all of a sudden?
你们怎么突然跑来找我了
I'm okay with anything but kissing.
接吻以下的行为我都能接受哦
I don't understand what you're saying.
我听不太懂妳在说什么呢…
Akagami is very afraid of you.
赤神很害怕妳
Oh dear.
哎呀呀
It seems like he's suffered some
他感觉好像受到过什么
severe psychological trauma.
剧烈的心理创伤一样
Oops, I kicked too hard.
不好 我踢得太猛了
If my friends and comrades aren't getting along, I can't sit back and do nothing.
我的挚友和战友关系不好 我可不能坐视不管
I want you two to be as close
我想让你们的关系
as Akagami and I are.
变得像我和赤神一样亲密呢
Isn't that a bit of a stretch?
妳这想法是不是有点一步登天了
Why don't you two
你们先跟彼此说说
share your impressions of each other first?
自己对对方的印象吧
Akagami, how do you feel when you see Kagura?
赤神 你见到神乐会有什么感受呢
Um… I get pains in my crotch.
嗯…我的胯下会感到疼痛
That's a blatant sexual harassment.
真是赤裸裸的性骚扰啊
This is a positive impression, Kagura.
这是正面印象哦 神乐
It's clearly a case of sexual harassment that could be taken to court.
妳也是个称职的裁判呢
Kagura, what do you think of Akagami?
神乐 妳是怎么看赤神的呢
Mr. Akagami is a good man.
赤神先生可是个好人呢
Yes.
对呀
Exactly.
没错没错
Akagami is a very impressive person.
赤神他可是非常出色的人呢
Not really.
没有啦
He's both serious and honest,
他既认真又诚实
which is why he has to be kicked out.
所以我才必须把他赶出去
Really, you both have pretty good impressions of each other.
真是的 你们对对方的印象 不是意外地很好吗
Let's move on to the final stage then.
那就让我们赶快进入最终阶段吧
You two will stay in the warehouse until tomorrow morning.
你们两个要在仓库待到明天早上哦
But it's morning now.
现在就是早上啊
It was here that Akagami and I cleared up our misunderstandings.
我和赤神就是在这里消除误会的
You two will definitely do well.
你们两个肯定也会相处得非常顺利
I'll have Twister ready by tonight.
晚上的时候我会准备好扭扭乐的
Miss Mia.
米亚小姐
We've been set up.
我们被摆了一道呢
I can't believe my plan has backfired on myself.
没想到我的计策 竟然反噬到自己身上来了
Indeed.
就是说啊
But luckily she didn't make me play
幸好她没有让我玩
the Hyakunin Isshu I casually taught her.
当时我随便教她的百人一首
Was that your doing as well?
原来那也是妳干的好事吗
Did Miss Mia get all of her outrageous knowledge from her?
米亚小姐那些离谱的知识 难道都是从她那里…
Oh, right.
啊 对了
If you harass me here,
如果我在这里被你侵犯了
I could easily get you kicked out of the temple.
那我就能很轻易地把你赶出寺庙了呢
Why didn't you tell Mia about my plan?
你为什么没有把我的计划告诉米亚呢
If you expose me, maybe I'll be cornered.
如果你揭穿了我 说不定就能我把逼入绝境了
I wouldn't do that.
我才不会那么做呢
I don't wish to be your enemy, Lord Kagura.
因为我并不想和神乐大人妳为敌
Lord?
大人…
The best thing is for us to get along.
如果我们能和睦相处的话 那就再好不过了
I want to cherish the… connection between us.
我想珍惜和妳之间的…缘分
What are you trying to do, buttering me up?
你在这刷我的好感度是要干什么呀
I'm not.
我并不是…
And you're keeping your distance from me.
而且你还离我这么远
I'm sorry. It's an involuntary reaction.
抱歉我的身体不由自主…
You should be buttering up Mia instead.
要刷的话 你就去刷米亚的好感度
Then take responsibility properly, and everything will be fine.
然后好好承担起责任 之后就什么事都没有了
Oh? Oh dear?
哎呀 哎呀呀
What's wrong?
妳怎么了
Nothing. Nothing at all.
没事…什么事都没有
She kicked it open.
她把门踹开了
This is the principle of leverage.
这就是杠杆原理哦
You clearly just kicked it.
分明就是妳踹开的
Why didn't I notice it earlier?
我为什么一直都没注意到呢
TAKE THIS I can take him away.
(把这个掠夺…) 我可以把他抓走啊
AND LIKE THIS I can get Akagami and Mia together,
(再这样) 我就把赤神和米亚撮合到一起
and then take him to Christoph's house later.
再把他带回去克莉丝多夫家吧
Akagami, let's get along.
赤神 我们好好相处吧
WORLDLY DESIRES
(世俗杂念)
(TenPuru -No one can live on loneliness-)
《妙庙美少女》
(Episode 10: It's Just That I'm a Little Horny)
(第十话) (只是有些欲火难平)
W-Wait a moment, Akagami.
等 等一下 赤神
Although we've kissed once before,
虽然我们之前有亲过一次了
I didn't mean to…
但我并不是想…
I've already said 'no.'
我都说了不行了
Please, Akagami.
拜托你了 赤神
At least…
至少…
be gentle with me.
对我温柔点…
No.
不要呀
Good morning, Sis Tsukuyo.
早安 月夜姐姐
Good morning, Kurage.
早安 海月
Let me go first.
总之 妳先放开我
Hmm.
好的
Please. I'll buy you a chocolate sundae if you keep my secret.
求求妳帮我保密吧 我会买给妳巧克力圣代的
I want a large one.
我要大份的
Alright.
好
How could I have such a dream?
我怎么会做那种梦呢
Is it because I'm horny?
难道我欲求不满了吗
Miss Tsukuyo.
月夜小姐
Good morning.
早安
Morning.
早
Alright, let's make breakfast.
好了 做早餐的时候到了
You look pretty relaxed.
他倒是一脸轻松
It's all because we kissed once
我会做那种梦
that I had such a dream.
说到底都是因为和他亲过一次的关系
But that was an accident.
不过那也是一场意外就是了
And it's all in the past now.
而且早就是过去式了
Akagami.
赤神
What's on the menu today?
今天都有什么菜呀
Breakfast will consist of grilled fish.
早上是烤鱼哦
Grilled fish.
烤鱼
By the way,
对了
Alright.
好
when did those two
他们是从什么时候开始
become so close?
变得那么要好的
APPLE JUICE That's really bothering me.
这件事确实很让人在意呢
Do you walk silently, Kagura?
神乐…妳走路怎么没声音
I think this might be an opportunity.
我觉得契机可能是这个哦
Camera?
摄影机…
Akagami, it's too tight.
赤神 太紧了…
Slow down a bit.
你再稍微慢一点啦
Where are we going, Miss Mia?
这才刚开始啊 米亚小姐
This is a kind of practice called Twister.
这是一种叫做扭扭乐的修行哦
Why are you showing me a pornographic video?
妳为什么要给我看色情影片啊
Was that Akagami and Mia?
刚才那是赤神和米亚吗
Yes, would you like to watch it again?
是的 妳要再看一次吗
No!
我不要看啦
They were glowing.
他们在发光呢
Did the two of them do it?
他们该不会做过了吧
No, no. At first,
不不不 一开始的时候
Mia really didn't like Akagami.
米亚可是很讨厌赤神的
SOY SAUCE Oh.
哎呀
I'm sorry, Akagami.
不好意思 赤神
I tripped.
我不小心绊到了脚
Are you alright, Miss Mia?
妳没事吧 米亚小姐
It's okay.
我没事
It's just that I'm a little horny.
我就是觉得有点欲火难平而已
Mia is definitely falling for him.
米亚绝对是迷上他了
And she even admitted to being horny.
而且她还说自己欲火难平
Let's start gathering evidence now.
现在开始调查取证
I'm the secretary, Kagura.
我是书记神乐
What's happened?
发生什么事了
Are you sure we don't need to call Akagami over?
我们真的不用把赤神也叫过来吗
No need, I don't want to see him now.
不用 我现在不想看见他
Speaking of, Kagura, are you interested in this matter?
话说神乐 妳也对这事感兴趣吗
I want to record everything related to Mia.
因为我想记录 所有和米亚有关的事情呀
Is that so? Well, do as you please.
是吗 那随妳便吧
There are reports that indecent activities have taken place in this temple.
其实我收到了 本寺出现伤风败俗之事的情报
And you, Mia, are the main suspect.
而且 米亚妳就是那个 有重大嫌疑的核心人物
I can't pretend I didn't hear that!
这我可不能当作没听见啊
I've never done anything against my conscience.
我从没做过一件违背自己良心的事情
So you're capable of answering any question?
那么 无论是什么问题 妳是否都能回答我呢
Of course.
那当然
Really? Then I have a question.
是吗…那我就问了
Mia, do you like Akagami?
米亚…妳喜欢赤神吗
-Uh… I wouldn't say so. -What?
-呃…也不算是吧… -啥
Why did you suddenly ask that?
妳为什么突然问我这个
Well.
居然
But you two have been getting closer and closer.
因为我感觉你们最近关系急速升温…
Ah! I see.
原来是这样啊
We're practice partners, so of course we get along.
因为我们是修行伙伴嘛 我们当然感情好呀
In that sense, I guess I do like him.
就这个方面来讲 我算是是喜欢他的
Oh.
哎呀
P-Partners?
伙…伴吗
At first, we did have misunderstandings and conflicts.
一开始我们确实有过误会和矛盾
But we've made up now.
但我们现在已经和解了
I see.
这样啊
So it was a misunderstanding.
原来是我的错觉吗
Also,
而且
Akagami is the world's most handsome man.
赤神不是世界第一美男子嘛
In fact, I came to Japan to develop my heart.
其实我来到日本的目的是修心
I've decided to eliminate my own distractions.
我已经决定要亲手消灭 自己的世俗杂念了
So Akagami is a very ideal partner.
所以说赤神在这一方面 是个非常理想的伙伴呢
Having such a handsome man by my side
毕竟有这么帅的帅哥在我身边嘛
constantly stirs up my distracting thoughts.
这样会刺激我产生杂念
Every day, I'm flipped and horny.
让我每天都小鹿乱撞欲火难平的
I felt destiny in this encounter.
在这场邂逅中 我感受到了命运
If possible, I'd even want to spend my lifetime with him.
如果可以的话 我甚至想和他共渡一生
The investigation continues.
我要继续进行调查取证了
What's wrong now?
又怎么了
Kagura! Why did you tie me up? Kagura!
神乐 妳为什么要把我绑起来 神乐
An encounter with destiny? Spending a lifetime together?
命运的邂逅…共渡一生…
This is
这已经
not as simple as liking someone!
不仅仅是喜欢了
Does Akagami know her thoughts? So he took advantage of her vulnerability.
赤神是知道她的想法 所以才会趁人之危做出那种事吗
But… but…
但是…但是…
He did this and that to me, too.
他也对我做了这样那样的事情
And…
而且…
I just want
总之我就是想
to make Miss Tsukuyo happy.
让月夜小姐获得幸福啊
Hasn't he said something like this?
他不是还说过这种话吗
Huh?
哎呀
Miss Tsukuyo, why is your face so red?
月夜小姐 妳的脸怎么这么红呀
A-Are you that angry?
妳 妳居然这么生气吗
It's not like that!
不是这样的
I'm not angry at all.
我才没生气呢
Well, that's me being rude.
哎呀 那是我唐突了呢
I thought
我还以为
you would definitely
月夜小姐妳肯定
be very jealous.
非常嫉妒呢
I have absolutely no feelings for Akagami…
我对赤神一点都不…
Did someone call me?
有人叫我吗
You guys seem to be having a lot of fun.
你们好像玩得很开心呀
Akagami.
赤神
Miss Mia.
米亚小姐…
What are you playing at?
她们是在玩什么呢
Miss Tsukuyo, what's going on?
月夜小姐 这究竟是…
Miss Tsukuyo?
月夜小姐
Your face is all red.
妳的脸真是红得像西红柿呢
What's going on?
到底是为什么呢
Don't look… at me.
别看…我
Did you do something you're ashamed of?
妳是做了什么没脸见人的事情吗
Do you want to try it, Akagami?
赤神 你要不要也加入我们呢
Please. Whoa!
请务必…呜哇
Akagami!
赤神
If that's the case, I'll confront him with the video.
既然如此 那我就直接拿影片质问他
Kagura! Hand me that evidence!
神乐 把那个证据给我
Okay.
好
Huh? Where did the camera go?
咦 我的摄影机跑去哪了
Uh, is this camera yours, Miss Kagura?
那个 这个摄影机是神乐姐姐的吗
Kurage!
海月
This is bad. That video is too pornographic.
不好 那个影片实在是太刺激了
Don't play it!
妳不要按播放啊
Play?
播放吗
I've said not to play it!
我都说了别播了
Absolutely do not watch!
妳绝对不可以看哦
They seem to be panting.
他们好像气喘吁吁的
Listen to me, Kurage!
妳可以好好听姐姐说话吗 海月
Innocent sister
我纯洁的妹妹
witnessing such indecent behavior.
居然看到了那么下流的行为
It seems this game is very interesting.
这个游戏看起来很有趣呢
What is that?
什么什么
Oh, this is when we have fun at the warehouse.
哦哦 这是在仓库玩的那个
So it was recorded.
原来被录下来了啊
Game?
你们说的游戏…
Look at the mat on the ground.
妳看地面上那个垫子
What? I thought…
什么呀 我还以为…
You thought?
还以为什么
What type of video did you think it was?
妳以为那是什么影片呢
I'll buy you a strawberry sundae, just don't ask.
我会买给妳草莓圣代的 妳就别问了
Why?
为什么
SNEAK AROUND, WITH EVIL INTENTION
(鬼鬼祟祟 来者不善)
No money!
没钱啊
The temple has more expenses than income during the New Year period,
跨年的时期寺庙总是入不敷出
and there is almost no incense money from worshippers.
而且好像也几乎没什么收到 参拜人员的香火钱
If this continues,
这样下去的话
where will the funds for Buddha's repairs come from?
主祀神的修理费要从哪弄来啊
No. No, I can't be disheartened.
不…不行不行 我不能灰心丧气
Let's start doing what I can do.
总之 我就先从我能做的开始做起吧
Firstly, save some food and such.
首先就是稍微节约一点粮食…
Ah!
啊呀呀呀
What happened, Akagami?
发生什么事了 赤神
I heard a princess-like scream!
我听到了公主般的悲鸣
Rice… rice…
白米…白米…
There is no more rice!
白米没有啦
What did you say?
你说什么
If there's no more rice, just go and buy some.
白米没有了的话 只要去买不就好了吗
That's easier said than done,
话是这么说没错
but there's no money.
但是我们没钱啊
Oh, that's the case.
原来是这样啊
But don't worry, Akagami.
不过你就放心吧 赤神
Japan has something called a yearly tribute, right?
日本不是有个叫做年贡的东西吗
Through this method, the temple can get rice for free.
通过这个方式 寺庙就能免费得到白米了
Miss Mia, what you're talking about isn't modern Japan.
米亚小姐 妳说的那个 并不是现代日本的习俗
What's wrong with you, Akagami?
赤神 你怎么了
I heard a princess-like scream.
我听到了公主般的悲鸣
Miss Yuzuki, actually the rice is already…
结月小姐 其实是米已经…
Finally finished?
终于吃完了吗
So,
那么
let's go collect the yearly tribute.
我们去收年贡吧
Seriously?
还真有这东西啊
Other temples do this too.
其他的寺庙也是这样的
There are a few properties under the name of Mikazuki Temple.
三日月寺名下有几处地产
We collect a certain amount of rice as a yearly tribute
所以我们会从使用那片地的人手中
from the people who use that land.
收取一定量的白米作为年贡
So it's something like rent?
也就是类似房租的东西吗
Roughly like that.
差不多是这样啦
Why is it still a yearly tribute and not money?
为什么现在不是收钱而是收年贡
Because the temple's business is essentially not for making money.
因为寺庙的事业 本质上就不是为了赚钱的
After all, the yearly tribute is just the goodwill of the parishioner.
说到底年贡也只是施主的好意罢了
I see.
原来如此…
You're not even close to learning, Akagami.
看来赤神你也学得还不够多呢
It's so frustrating.
好强烈的挫败感…
But,
不过
is it really okay for us to go with you?
我们跟妳一起去真的没关系吗
Won't it seem a bit impolite?
这样会不会有点没礼貌
Of course, it's okay.
当然没关系啦
And rice is heavy, so I need help.
更何况白米很重 所以我也需要人手帮忙
And visiting parishioners is also
而且拜访施主
part of the practice.
也是修行的一环哦
Practice?
什么修行
The fourth component of enlightenment is to cherish
最初开悟的心得 其四
and appreciate all of one's destinies in the present moment.
珍惜感谢当下一切的缘分
All things are connected by destiny.
(缘份) 一切事情都是因缘分而相连结的
There is not a single thing that is meaningless.
(因果 连结) 没有一件事是毫无意义的
Mia, your visit to Mikazuki Temple
米亚妳来到三日月寺
and Akagami's employment here
赤神你来这里工作
are not coincidental occurrences.
这些事情都不是偶然发生的
-This… -Indeed.
-这个… -确实啊…
Destinies are crucial.
缘分是非常重要的事物
We have to be grateful for them every day.
所以我们每天都要对它心怀感激才行
Because of various destiny,
我们接下来要去见的人
the people we are about to meet became Mikazuki Temple devotees.
他们也是因为各种机缘巧合 才成为三日月寺的施主的
MIKAZUKI TEMPLE So,
所以说
what kind of people are our temples for?
我们的寺庙 究竟是为了什么人而存在的
We will get to know them well.
接下来我们就要好好了解一番呢
Alright.
好
Then let us confirm and express our heartfelt gratitude!
那我们就好好了解一番 并献上满满的感激之情吧
I have no rice at home, go back where you came from.
我家才没米咧 给我滚回去
Get lost.
滚
-Miss Yuzuki? -Let's go to the next house.
-结月小姐 -我 我们去下一家吧
Isn't it funny that you're still collecting tribute these days?
现在还收年贡是不是有点搞笑了
Grampy, please give us some rice.
老爷爷 请给我们点米
The yearly tributes.
我说的是年贡
If you clean for me, I'll give you some.
你们要是给我打扫卫生我就给你们
Why are we cleaning? Is this also a destiny?
为什么我们在打扫卫生呢 这也是缘分吗
Haha.
啊哈哈
The closet is too full. It can't hold anymore!
壁橱的空间已经到达极限啦
What's all this about?
这到底是怎么回事
In the end, we didn't get any rice.
到最后我们也没拿到米
Well,
那个
the yearly tribute was originally sent voluntarily by parishioners each year.
其实年贡本来应该是施主 每年主动送过来给我们的
Those we visited today have been delaying the yearly tributes for various reasons.
我们今天去的那几家 因为某些原因的关系所以一直拖欠着
Does that mean they also have difficulties?
也就是说他们是有什么难处吗
Uh… sort of.
呃…算是吧
Next house! The next house is the last one.
下一家 下一家是最后一家了哦
Cheer up and let's go.
我们打起精神出发吧
Welcome, Yuzuki. Thank you for coming all the way out here.
是结月啊 欢迎欢迎 麻烦妳特地跑一趟了啊
We're sorry to bother you.
我们才是多多打扰了
No problem at all.
没事没事
This is my first time seeing you two.
这两位是我第一次见呢
Thanks for coming all this way. I accidentally broke my leg.
我家这么远还麻烦你们亲自过来 都怪我不小心把腿摔断了
The rice is in the yard.
白米就在院子里
Take as much as you want.
你们想要多少就拿多少吧
Lady Buddha!
女菩萨
What? Am I that beautiful?
什么什么 我有那么漂亮吗
Your children are so cute.
您的孩子都好可爱啊
Mom.
妈妈
Do we have guests?
有客人吗
Ah! It's Sis Yuzuki.
啊 是结月姐姐
Yo.
嗨
So cute.
哎呀 真可爱
Welcome.
欢迎你们
Oh, do you want to play a game?
我们要玩些什么游戏吗
Wow!
哇
Don't mess around, she is very busy.
你们别捣乱 姐姐可是很忙的
Then,
那…
show us your breasts!
给我们看看妳的胸部
Dream on.
做梦
-They're always so annoying. -Breasts!
-他们每次都这么折腾人呢 -胸部 胸部...
Sorry. These two brats are far too obsessed with breasts.
抱歉 这两个小鬼 实在是太喜欢胸部了
Breasts!
胸部
Why are they so eager to see breasts?
他们怎么就那么想看胸部呢
They must really want to see…
那肯定是很想看...
Akagami!
赤神
Why are my thoughts on par with the children's?
我的想法居然和小孩 在同一个级别吗
This is not a good thing, kids!
这可不是什么好事啊 小朋友们
If you keep doing this, you will not be able to become outstanding adults.
你们这样是不能 成为出色的成年人的
Only by overcoming one's own desires
只有战胜自己的欲望
can one mature properly.
人才能正确的成长
Is that so?
是吗…
I got it, sis.
我明白了 姐姐
It's great that you got it.
你们明白就好
So,
所以
show us the breasts of an outstanding adult.
给我们看看出色的大人的胸部吧
How did it come to this?
怎么会变成这样
Show us.
给我们看看嘛
Oh no, this is bad.
哎呀…不好了
You're Akagami, right?
你就是赤神吧
Yuzuki has mentioned you.
我有听结月提到过你
I apologize for not greeting you sooner. My name is Akagami.
抱歉我刚才没和您打招呼 我叫赤神
Nice to meet you.
还请您多多关照
Sorry for the sudden commotion.
闹成这样真是不好意思呀
It's fine. You are already far superior to the other parishioners.
没事没事 和其他施主相比 您这里已经好很多了
Do they all have bad attitudes?
哎呀 前面几家态度都很差吗
Honestly, I want to cut ties with them.
老实讲 我都想和他们断缘了
You're quite interesting.
你还蛮有趣的嘛
But it wasn't like this before.
不过以前可不是这样的
When Tsukina… Yuzuki's mother was around,
月那师姐… 也就是结月的母亲还在的时候
no one dared to delay their yearly tribute.
可没有人敢拖欠年贡呢
Tsukina was super scary.
月那师姐超级可怕的呢
I've been punched by her several times.
就连我都挨过她的拳头呢
But… at that time, it actually felt reassuring.
不过…那时反而让人有种放心的感觉
Everyone is very uneasy now.
大家现在都感到很不安
Since Tsukina left the temple,
自从月那师姐离开了寺庙
everyone has been wondering about the future of Mikazuki Temple.
大家都在想三日月寺 今后会何去何从呢
Why did she leave the temple?
她为什么会离开寺庙呢
I'm not very clear about that.
这我就不太清楚了
I only heard that she is now living near the Head Temple.
我只听说她现在住在总寺院那边
Akagami!
赤神
Breasts are great!
胸部超棒
Great, great.
超棒超棒
Enough of that, you little perverts.
你们真是够了 小色鬼们
I'm really sorry about today.
今天真是不好意思
Though an apology isn't going to do much.
虽然道歉也没什么用
That's a lot.
这么多啊
This rice is heavy, be careful.
这些米很重的 你们要小心哦
It is indeed heavy.
确实很重
The rice bag…
米袋...
I feel like I've seen it somewhere.
感觉我好像在哪里见过
Back then…
那时候…
What is it, Akagami?
你怎么了 赤神
It's nothing.
没事
I-I just felt a destiny.
我只是在刚刚感受到了缘分
I see.
是吗
Yes… I should be grateful for that encounter.
没错…我要感谢那次相遇
And fully support Miss Yuzuki.
并且全力支持结月小姐
Let's go home.
我们回家吧
It's just like Yuzuki.
真不愧是结月
Does she really… need help?
她真的…需要支持吗
(Next Episode: The Body is Very Honest)
(下一话 身体是很诚实的哦)
What did you dream about for your first dream of the New Year?
新年第一梦妳梦到什么啦
I dreamed about Akagami swinging around.
我梦到赤神哥哥晃晃甩甩的
What was swinging around?
(下一话 身体是很诚实的哦) 什么晃晃甩甩的
Sis Yuzuki and Sis Tsukuyo were also there.
结月姐姐和月夜姐姐也是
Doing what?
(下一话 身体是很诚实的哦) 到底是什么
Everyone was swinging around, loving each other.
大家一起晃晃甩甩亲亲爱爱
Loving each other…
(下一话 身体是很诚实的哦) 亲亲爱爱…